Diane Di Prima Papers
Diane Di Prima Papers
- Miscellaneous material
  - Press release regarding the Floating Bear obscenity case, 1961
Hakkert, Arie 1965 Sep 15 (carbon) (to Mrs. Diane diPrima Marlowe)
Hall, Barry L. * 1970 Feb 6 * 1970 Sep 7 * 1971 Apr 15 * 1971 Apr 19
Hanna, Charles S. 1970 Aug 20
Haynes, Michael 1971 Feb 20 (note on an index card)
Heinz, Drue 1969 Apr 21 (to Alan S. Marlowe, enclosed in Marlowe to diPrima, 1969 May 2)
Heinz, Mrs. [ ] * 1969 Jun 6
Henderson, David 1968 Dec 31 * 1971 Jan 11 (attached are typescript carbon of the poems "to M.," "The Henderson Report on Science Convention in Dallas 1969" (2 pp.) and "Hanging out in the Music, Poem 1," the first two signed by the poet.) 1971 Jan 13
Herms, George 1970 Aug 20 (postcard)
Heyman, George undated
Hoffman, Jack 1970 Sep 18
Jackrell, T.L. 1969 Jul 31
Jones, LeRoi (signed as Miles Campion, pseudonym) undated (to "Sirs" [Floating Bear, Diane DiPrima])
Jordan, Fred 1970 Aug 3 1971 Jan 6
Kelly, Aby * 1969 Jul 26
Kelly, Robert * 1961 Jun 12 1961 Sep 20 (postcard) * 1961 Nov 22 1970 Dec 26 (postcard)
Kirby, Brian 1969 Aug 21
Knox, Hugh * 1969 Mar 27
Kupferburg, Tuli * 1971 Apr 26
Lake, Larry 1971 Feb 17 (postcard) 1971 Mar (postcard) 1971 Apr 6 (postcard)
Lansing, Gerrit 1970 Aug 20
Laughlin, James 1969 Jul 28 (postcard)
Lawlor, Deb * 1971 May 21
Lee, Deborah & Bob undated (note)
Levertov, Denise 1961 Nov 16 (to LeRoi [Jones], Hettie [Cohen], and Diane [diPrima])
Loewinsohn,Ron * 1970 Dec 21
Longville, Tim * 1969 Apr 21
Lowell, Robert 1961 Dec 2 (postcard)
Lowenfels, Walter * 1962 Jan 30 (card) * 1962 Sep 11 1968 May 23 1968 Aug 1
MacAdam, Lewis undated
McClure, Keera * 1961 Jul 27 1961 Nov 9 (postcard) * 1962 Mar 28 1962 Aug 12 (postcard)
McClure, Michael * 1960 Sep 15 * 1961 Jan 8 1961 Mar 23 (postcard) * 1961 Apr 5 * 1961 Apr 15 (includes ts of 5 poems) * 1961 Jun 6 * 1961 Jun 28 (on a card) * 1961 Jul 10 (to Diane [diPrima] and Peter) *1961 Jul 17 1961 Jul 18 (postcard) 1961 Jul 22 (postcard) * 1961 Jul 27 1961 Jul 27? 1961 Dec 15 (postcard) * 1962 Mar 10 * 1963 Mar 7 * 1963 Jul 10 (to Frank O'Hara) * 1963 Jul 24
McDaniel, Zella * 1971 Jan 18
MacDonald, Dwight 1961 Nov 20
McSilvers [?], Larry 1971 Mar 25 (postcard)
Malanga, Gerard * 1969 Apr 9
Marlowe, Alan ("Daddy") undated (to Alex) undated Thanksgiving 1968 (postcard) * 1968 Nov 20 (with two-page typescript poem attached) * 1968 Nov 21 * 1968 Nov 22 * 1968 Nov 25 1968 Nov 26 1968 Nov 30 * 1968 Dec 14 1969 Apr 29 (postcard) 1969 Apr 30 * 1969 May 2 (enclosed: Drue Heinz to Alan S. Marlowe, 1969 Apr 21) 1969 May 3 (postcard) 1969 May 5 (postcard) * 1969 May 7 * 1969 May 9 1969 May 11 (postcard) 1969 May 12 (postcard) 1969 May 19 (postcard) * 1969 May 29 1969 Jun 1 1969 Jun 4 * 1969 Jun 7 1969 Jun 8 (postcard) 1969 Jun 9 (2 postcards of the same date) 1969 Jun 14 (postcard) 1969 Jun 27 (on postcard of Fields Book Store to Kyle Alexander) * 1969 Jul 4 1969 Jul 6 (postcard) 1969 Jul 12 (postcard) 1969 Jul 15 (with a two page typescript of poem "For Frank O'Hara") 1969 Jul 17 (postcard) 1969 Jul 21 (to Brian Kirby) * 1969 Jul 24 1969 Jul 27 1969 Jul 27 (postcard) 1969 Jul 28 (postcard) 1969 Jul 29 (postcard) * 1969 Jul 30 1969 Aug 2 (postcard) 1969 Aug 5 (postcard) 1969 Aug 5 (postcard) 1969 Aug 7 (postcard) 1969 Aug 19 (postcard) * 1969 Sep 2 * 1969 Sep 16 * 1969 Sep 25 1969 Oct 13 * 1969 Oct 18 (with enclosure) 1969 Oct 23 1969 Oct 31 (postcard) 1969 Nov 4 1969 Nov 10 1969 Nov 12 (postcard) * 1969 Nov 20 * 1969 Nov 25 * 1969 Dec 7 1969 Dec 9 * 1970 Jan 5 1970 Jan 8 * 1970 Jan 19 * 1970 Jan 25 1970 Jan 26 1970 Jan 29 (postcard) 1970 Jan 30 1970 Feb 5 (postcard) 1970 Feb 5 (postcard) 1970 Feb 9 (with note card attached) 1970 Feb 17 (postcard) * 1970 Feb 21 * 1970 Feb 25 1970 Mar 13 (postcard) * 1970 Mar 14 1970 Mar 16 (postcard) * 1970 Mar 30 * 1970 Apr 4 (with three-page typescript poem attached) * 1970 Jul 2 * 1970 Jul 9 * 1970 Sep 3 * 1970 Sep 11 1970 Sep 13 * 1970 Sep 17 * 1970 Oct 7 * 1970 Oct 14 * 1970 Oct 24 (with attached typescript of poem "Hard Practice") 1970 Nov 7 1970 Nov 12 (postcard) 1970 Nov 17 1970 Nov 18 (postcard) 1970 Nov 25 * 1970 Dec 9 ?1971 Jan ?1971 Jan 22 1971 Feb 2 1971 Feb 8 1971 Feb 23
Mee, Charles L. Jr. * 1962 Nov 9
Meehan, Patricia A. 1970 Jun 4
Meltzer, David * 1961 Sep 14 * 1961 Sep 23 * 1961 Oct 20 * 1961 Nov 1962 Feb 13 (postcard) 1971 Mar 22 (postcard)
Menza, Claudia * 1971 Feb 9
Merwin, W.S. ("Bill") 1963 Feb 28 (to Roi [LeRoi Jones])
Miles, B. 1969 May 23
Morris, James Ryan undated undated undated 1969 May 15 (postcard) * 1969 Oct 1 * 1970 Nov 9 1971 Jan 1971 Jan 24 1971 Feb 9 (postcard) * 1971 Feb 19 1971 May 5 (postcard)
Motherwell, Robert 1962 Feb 10 (postcard)
Mules, B. 1969 May 23
New Directions 1971 Mar 18 1971 Mar 24
Nomland, John 1968 May 23
Nunnelee, Mark 1970 Oct 9 * 1970 Nov 3 1970 Nov 10 (postcard) * 1970 Dec 17 * 1971 Feb 8 (Attached are photocopies of 2 ts poems, "Swansong" and an untitled "I have tried more than once...") * 1971 Mar 11 1971 Apr 12
Olson, Charles * 1961 Nov 1 (to Diane [diPrima] and LeRoi [Jones])
Olympia Press see Maurice Girodias see David Young
Oppen, Mary 1971 Apr 12 (postcard)
Parrett, Jerry * 1969 Apr 17
Partisan Review see William Phillips
Patchen, Kenneth & Mariam undated (note on an unmailed postcard)
Perkins, Michael * 1969 Oct 2 * 1970 Aug 25
Perkoff, Stuart Z. 1968 Jan 26
Phillips, William * 1969 Jul 17
Prensky, Paul * 1969 Jul 24
Puvapalli, Sontashiri 1971 Feb (postcard)
Reed, Sweeney 1969 Jul 22
Rexroth, Kenneth * 1969 Aug 8
Rumaker, Mike * 1961 Aug 8
Silver, Nancy see Fred Jordan
Snyder, Don 1971 Jan
Sottsass, Pivano * 1969 Jul 29
Soyer, Rebecca & Raphael undated (on a Christmas card)
Soyer, Raphael * 1971 Apr 13
Standard, Michael B. * 1971 Jan 15
Su Wa, Yu see Yu Suwa
University of North Carolina Library 1969 Apr 18 (to Poets Press [Diane diPrima])
Van Newkirk, Allen * 1969 Jul 7 * 1971 Jan 29 1971 Mar 1 (postcard)
Vas Dias, Robert * 1969 Jun 1
Villiers Publications, Ltd. 1971 Jun 1 (to Lawrence [Ferlinghetti])
Voitlee, Bob * 1969 May 4
Wagner, Dave 1968 May 18 (postcard, to Poets Press [Diane diPrima])
Wakoski, Diane 1962 Aug 30 (to Editors, The Floating Bear)
Waldman, Anne n.d (postcard) undated (note on an unmailed postcard) * 1968 Dec 13 1969 Mar 21 (postcard) 1970 Dec 10 (postcard) 1971 Jan 7 (postcard) * 1971 Feb 1 1971 Feb 9
Wallrich, Larry & Ruby 1971 (New Year greeting card, unsigned)
Wallrich, Larry A. 1971 Mar 17 1971 Apr (postcard)
Waring, J. * 1962 Nov 22 * 1970 Jun 14
Webb, Jon 1968 Jan 7 (with an attached enclosure)
Webb, Jon & Louise 1971 Jan 26 (postcard)
Webern, Anton (signed as) undated (to Lieber "Bar") undated
Whalen, Philip undated
Wieners, John n.y. Apr 1 (to Billy [ ])
Willems, James R. * 1971 Mar 24
Williams, Galen * 1971 Jan 19
Wilson, Mark * 1971 Feb 11
Wilson, Robert A. n.y. Dec 8 (postcard) 1970 Aug 25 (postcard)
Wylie, Andrew * 1971 Feb 9
Young, David * 1970 Aug 17
Yu Suwa undated undated
Zukofsky, Louis * 1961 Sep 15 1962 Mar 17 (postcard) * 1962 Oct 20 (to Diane [diPrima] and LeRoi [Jones])
---, Anthony 1969 Nov 3
---, Becki 1970 Dec 18 (postcard)
---, David and Maria undated (card)
---, David 1971 Apr
---, Diane * 1971 Mar 5 1971 Mar 6 (typed note) undated (2 items)
---, Donna, Alan, and Nye 1971 Mar 12
---, Ellen 1971 Mar 4 (postcard)
---, Graham 1971 (postcard)
---, Harriet 1971 Jun 4 (postcard)
---, Idell undated (postcard) 1971 Mar (postcard) * 1971 Mar 11 1971 Mar 31 (postcard)
---, Joby * 1971 Jan 15
---, John 1968 Jun 18 (postcard) 1971 Apr 21
---, Julia n.y. Mar 28
---, Mel 1968 Apr 15
---, Reggie n.y. Nov 7 * 1970 Jul 23 * 1970 Aug 10
---, Rudi * 1971 Jan 9
---, Sam undated
---, [Steve?] 1971 Apr 19
---, Ted 1970 Nov 28
---, Wynn 1971 Feb 7 (postcard, to Sally, Sam & Sarah)